# Steven Modimo

# Full Stack Web Developer



- ✓ freelancer.stevenmodimo@gmail.com
- +255746594790
- Arusha, Tanzania
- EstebanPierre
- steven10#6248

#### **PROFILE**

I am full stack web developer with experience in building web based online solutions that can impact business and provide help to groups in need all over the world. I like to build stuffs that impact people on various aspects of life.

# **LANGUAGES**

English  $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$ Swahili  $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$ 

# **SKILLS**

**Web apps** ● ● ● ● ● ■ I can build websites from the user interface to a complete backend system with database intergrations

API Design • • • • •

# **INTERESTS**

Reading, Writing, Cooking

#### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

# **Lupenet, Backend Developer**

2021 - 2021 | Nairobi, Kenya

#### Habari Node, Full stack engineer

2021 - 2022 | Kampala, Uganda

# **Tech One, Database Administrator**

2022 - present | Nairobi, Kenya

#### **EDUCATION**

Online Bootcamp, freecodecamp.org *⊗* 2019 – 2021

**Computer Science, Arusha Technical College** 

# **CERTIFICATES**

- Backend Developer and API Designer ∂
- Frontend Developement Libraries 🔗
- Responsive Web Desing ∅
- Javascript Developer ∂